1. openBrowser("")
5. navigateToUrl("https://advantageonlineshopping.com/#/")
9. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Record/Register/Page_Advantage Shopping/svg_CHECKOUT  (0.00)_menuUser"))
13. delay(3)
17. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Record/Register/Page_Advantage Shopping/a_CREATE NEW ACCOUNT"))
21. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Record/Register/Page_Advantage Shopping/input__usernameRegisterPage"), "test")
25. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Record/Register/Page_Advantage Shopping/input__emailRegisterPage"), "mail.com")
29. setEncryptedText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Record/Register/Page_Advantage Shopping/input__passwordRegisterPage"), "NOZHw6sL/1I=")
33. setEncryptedText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Record/Register/Page_Advantage Shopping/input__confirm_passwordRegisterPage"), "NmLWqEVKCcs=")
37. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Record/Register/Page_Advantage Shopping/div_ACCOUNT DETAILS                        _b895da"))
41. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Record/Register/Page_Advantage Shopping/input_Receive exclusive offers and promotio_5c7450"))
45. verifyTextPresent("Use 5 character or longer", false)
49. verifyTextPresent("Your email address isn't formatted correctly", false)
53. verifyTextPresent("One upper letter required", false)
57. verifyTextPresent("Passwords do not match", false)
61. verifyElementNotClickable(findTestObject("Object Repository/Record/Register/Page_Advantage Shopping/button_REGISTER"))
65. closeBrowser()